<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://docs.horizonnetworks.uk/es/blog</id>
    <title>HRZN Hosting Knowledgebase Blog</title>
    <updated>2022-12-23T22:20:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://docs.horizonnetworks.uk/es/blog"/>
    <subtitle>HRZN Hosting Knowledgebase Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://docs.horizonnetworks.uk/es/https://archive.horizonnetworks.uk/Branding/Logo/Coloured_Icon.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Holidays from the Horizon Team]]></title>
        <id>https://docs.horizonnetworks.uk/es/blog/december_2022_christmas_announcement</id>
        <link href="https://docs.horizonnetworks.uk/es/blog/december_2022_christmas_announcement"/>
        <updated>2022-12-23T22:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year has been a very big year for us at Horizon. We thank all clients for their continued support of Horizon Hosting. To say thank you, we are holding a 25% off sale this holiday period.  Use code HAPPYHOLIDAYS2022 on any new order!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This year has been a very big year for us at Horizon. We thank all clients for their continued support of Horizon Hosting. To say thank you, we are holding a 25% off sale this holiday period. <!-- --> Use code <code>HAPPYHOLIDAYS2022</code> on any new order!</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="uk-machine-upgrade">UK machine upgrade<a href="#uk-machine-upgrade" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al UK machine upgrade" title="Enlace directo al UK machine upgrade">​</a></h2><p>On the 10th of December, Horizon Management travelled to a datacentre in the Midlands to install a new Ryzen 9 5900X based system which will allow for increased performance and capacity for our UK-based customers. This £2,000 investment will be very beneficial, and is a significant milestone for our company. </p><p>All UK-based clients will be upgraded to this system free-of-charge in the near future - the maintenance period will be announced separately.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="web-hosting">Web Hosting<a href="#web-hosting" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Web Hosting" title="Enlace directo al Web Hosting">​</a></h2><p>Horizon are constantly looking to improve our services where possible. We currently have plans to perform an upgrade to our web hosting systems, as well as bringing in more packages to allow you to host larger websites!</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="support-over-the-christmas-period">Support over the Christmas Period<a href="#support-over-the-christmas-period" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Support over the Christmas Period" title="Enlace directo al Support over the Christmas Period">​</a></h2><p>Support will be limited on the 25th, 26th and 27th of December, to allow the Horizon team to enjoy the Christmas period. Support responses may be delayed or not available at all.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="2023">2023<a href="#2023" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al 2023" title="Enlace directo al 2023">​</a></h2><p>We at the Horizon team are very optimistic for 2023. We will continue our efforts with the rebranding, as well as putting more development time into things like our Pat Panel, as well as our website.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="afterword">Afterword<a href="#afterword" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Afterword" title="Enlace directo al Afterword">​</a></h2><p>From all of us at Horizon Hosting, have a good Christmas and a Happy New Year.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Mackenzie D</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/Mack29446</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica S</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/LoGaming</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="updates" term="updates"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new Horizon Hosting]]></title>
        <id>https://docs.horizonnetworks.uk/es/blog/the_new_horizon</id>
        <link href="https://docs.horizonnetworks.uk/es/blog/the_new_horizon"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the world moves forward, so should Horizon Networks. That's why over the coming months, changes will be made to improve our services for everyone!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As the world moves forward, so should Horizon Networks. That's why over the coming months, changes will be made to improve our services for everyone!</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="rebranding">Rebranding<a href="#rebranding" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Rebranding" title="Enlace directo al Rebranding">​</a></h2><p>First of all, we are giving Horizon Networks a revamp!</p><p>We are now known as HRZN / Horizon Hosting. This decision has been made to support the future of the business, and how we would like to grow in the future.
With this change comes our updated branding, which can all be found <a href="https://archive.horizonnetworks.uk/Branding/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>. You will see these logos and our new
up to date colour scheme pop up across our sites slowly during the coming months. We also aim to make our user interfaces clean and consistent throughout, enabling
you to have a pleasent experience.</p><div class="theme-admonition theme-admonition-info alert alert--info admonition_LlT9"><div class="admonitionHeading_tbUL"><span class="admonitionIcon_kALy"><svg viewBox="0 0 14 16"><path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M7 2.3c3.14 0 5.7 2.56 5.7 5.7s-2.56 5.7-5.7 5.7A5.71 5.71 0 0 1 1.3 8c0-3.14 2.56-5.7 5.7-5.7zM7 1C3.14 1 0 4.14 0 8s3.14 7 7 7 7-3.14 7-7-3.14-7-7-7zm1 3H6v5h2V4zm0 6H6v2h2v-2z"></path></svg></span>info</div><div class="admonitionContent_S0QG"><p>A full HRZN Hosting branding page is currently in the works.</p></div></div><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="software">Software<a href="#software" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Software" title="Enlace directo al Software">​</a></h2><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="pat-panel">Pat Panel<a href="#pat-panel" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Pat Panel" title="Enlace directo al Pat Panel">​</a></h3><p>Our Pat Panel will start to receive some gradual updates in the future, as we ramp up development!</p><p>This will include updating to our new branding, colour scheme and UI standards as well as lots of new features to improve your experience!</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="website">Website<a href="#website" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Website" title="Enlace directo al Website">​</a></h3><p>We are also going to reintroduce our main website, as it was a great way to advertise what we have to offer, and what you can expect from our services.</p><p>It was a great way to help customers understand our services, and why we are a good fit for them.</p><p>Along with this, we will be updating the billing panel to match our website's UI design, for seamless navigation!</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="transparency">Transparency<a href="#transparency" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Transparency" title="Enlace directo al Transparency">​</a></h2><p>Secondly, we want to be more transparent with our customers.
Every piece of maintenance and downtime should have a brief incident report written, to help our customers understand where we slipped up, and what we will do in the future. This will also be met with a consistent and published set of compensation rules.
Also, we will make sure to post yearly and quaterly transparency reports so everyone interested can look what has been going on for us!
Overall, we will help gain trust with our customers and help them know exactly what is going on as much as possible!</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="privacy-and-security">Privacy and security<a href="#privacy-and-security" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Privacy and security" title="Enlace directo al Privacy and security">​</a></h2><p>Finally, we want to help increase privacy and security to our internal services and customer servers.
We will start by removing all our current tracking and analytics solutions, and replace them with a new privacy focused solution.
Also, we are assessing our internal protocol for password sharing and infastructure access, and improving this as much as possible to protect everyone's servers and software!</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="afterword">Afterword<a href="#afterword" class="hash-link" aria-label="Enlace directo al Afterword" title="Enlace directo al Afterword">​</a></h2><p>Thank you for choosing Horizon, and we hope to improve our services for everyone, any suggestions are greatly appreciated!
As Horizon begins to expand, we want to do things right!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Luca T</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/LucaTanks</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Hayden S</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/Hayden1321</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="updates" term="updates"/>
        <category label="important" term="important"/>
        <category label="business" term="business"/>
    </entry>
</feed>